[
    {
        "question": "In 2018, what was the percentage of women in the tech industry?",
        "additionInfo": "One of the reasons why there is a lower percentage of women working in the tech industry compared to other industries is that girls are less likely to study STEM subjects compared to boys.",
        "optionA": "15%", 
        "optionB": "48%",       
        "optionC": "28%",
        "optionD": "35%",
        "answer": "optionC",
        "points": 1, 
        "number": 1
    },

    {
        "question": "Girls are less likely to study STEM subjects than boys. In 2018, what percentage of girls were enrolled in engineering courses while in college?",
        "additionInfo": "The gender disparity that starts in high school and university becomes even more pronounced when it comes to making career choices.",
        "optionA": "2%", 
        "optionB": "12%",       
        "optionC": "34%",
        "optionD": "6%",
        "answer": "optionA",
        "points": 2,
        "number": 2
    },

    {
        "question": "What is the average salary for software engineers in canada?",
        "additionInfo": "",
        "optionA": "$52k", 
        "optionB": "$68k",       
        "optionC": "$75k",
        "optionD": "$38k",
        "answer": "optionC",
        "points": 2,
        "number": 3
    },

    {
        "question": "What is true in regards to being carbon neutral?",
        "additionInfo": "",
        "optionA": "Carbon neutral means achieving net zero carbon dioxide emissions by balancing carbon dioxide emissions with removal or simply eliminating carbon dioxide emissions altogether", 
        "optionB": "Attempting to be carbon neutral is really expensive",       
        "optionC": "A company’s carbon footprint can be forgiven by donating large amounts to environmental groups",
        "optionD": "Planting trees in the tropics is more cost effective and is more effective than a company going carbon neutral",
        "answer": "optionA",
        "points": 2,
        "number": 4
    },

    {
        "question": "Which one of these skincare and makeup companies is carbon neutral?",
        "additionInfo": "",
        "optionA": "Fenty Beauty", 
        "optionB": "Versed",       
        "optionC": "Urban Decay",
        "optionD": "Neutrogena",
        "answer": "optionB",
        "points": 2,
        "number": 5
    },

    {
        "question": "What are ways to encourage young women to get involved in the tech industry?",
        "additionInfo": "",
        "optionA": "Encourage them to attend fun events likeSheHacks", 
        "optionB": "Provide mentorship",       
        "optionC": "Provide scholarships and grants to further their education",
        "optionD": "All of the above",
        "answer": "optionD",
        "points": 2,
        "number": 6
    },

    {
        "question": "What are the benefits to opening a savings account?",
        "additionInfo": "",
        "optionA": "Deposited funds accrue interest over time", 
        "optionB": "A secure place to store your money",       
        "optionC": "Banks place limits on the number of withdrawals allowed, which encourages saving over spending",
        "optionD": "All of the above",
        "answer": "optionD",
        "points": 2,
        "number": 7
    },

    {
        "question": "What is the importance of creating a budget?",
        "additionInfo": "",
        "optionA": "By creating a spending plan it will ensure that you have enough money for important things like bills and food", 
        "optionB": "For other people to think you know what to do with money",       
        "optionC": "It is not important, spend your money on what you want",
        "optionD": "Creating a budget takes a lot of time is not worth it",
        "answer": "optionA",
        "points": 2,
        "number": 8
    },

    {
        "question": " Which American software company designed the highly popular and innovative personal finance app Mint?",
        "additionInfo": "Finance apps are one of the best creations the tech industry has developed for managing personal finances. They can connect to your bank account and keep track of your spending.",
        "optionA": "Microsoft", 
        "optionB": "Intuit",       
        "optionC": "IBM",
        "optionD": "Apple",
        "answer": "optionB",
        "points": 2,
        "number": 9
    },

    {
        "question": "What would make a bad candidate for investing?",
        "additionInfo": "There are many types of investments such as stocks, bonds, ETFs, mutual funds, cash equivalents, real estate, REITs and commodities. (Wealthsimple.com)",
        "optionA": "Having an emergency fund", 
        "optionB": "Having a stable income with extra money (after bills)",       
        "optionC": "Having a lot of credit card debt",
        "optionD": "Being a full time employee at a company",
        "answer": "optionC",
        "points": 2,
        "number": 10
    },

    {
        "question": "When was the first computer game invented? Hint: it was called “Tennis For Two",
        "additionInfo": "",
        "optionA": "1958", 
        "optionB": "1987",       
        "optionC": "1904",
        "optionD": "1995",
        "answer": "optionA",
        "points": 2,
        "number": 11
    },

    {
        "question": "What does HTML stand for? Hint/additional info: this language is used to design website layouts",
        "additionInfo": "",
        "optionA": "Heavytest Media Language", 
        "optionB": "Halo Time Music Language",       
        "optionC": "Hightext Modification Language",
        "optionD": "Hypertext Markup Language",
        "answer": "optionD",
        "points": 2,
        "number": 12
    },

    {
        "question": "What can a debit card do/have that a credit card cannot?",
        "additionInfo": "",
        "optionA": "Make payments", 
        "optionB": "Withdraw money",       
        "optionC": "Associated with chequing account",
        "optionD": "Redeem rewards",
        "answer": "optionC",
        "points": 2,
        "number": 13
    },

    {
        "question": "Who was the first female game programmer?",
        "additionInfo": "",
        "optionA": "Naomi Brooks", 
        "optionB": "Carol Shaw",       
        "optionC": "Ada Lovelace",
        "optionD": "Mary Jackson",
        "answer": "optionB",
        "points": 2,
        "number": 14
    },

    {
        "question": "As of 2020, which is the world’s biggest tech company?",
        "additionInfo": "",
        "optionA": "Sony", 
        "optionB": "Apple",       
        "optionC": "Microsoft",
        "optionD": "Mary Jackson",
        "answer": "optionD",
        "points": 2,
        "number": 15
    }

]